<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>11s on</title><link>https://www.dhammacharts.org/quartz/11/</link><description>Recent content in 11s on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://www.dhammacharts.org/quartz/11/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>11 benefits to practicing metta</title><link>https://www.dhammacharts.org/quartz/11/11-benefits-to-practicing-metta/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.dhammacharts.org/quartz/11/11-benefits-to-practicing-metta/</guid><description>(loving-kindness) meditation / prayer:
You will sleep easily You will wake easily You will have pleasant dreams People will love you Devas (gods or angels) and animals will love you Devas will protect you External dangers, such as poisons, weapons, and fire, will not harm you Your face will be radiant Your mind will be serene You will die unconfused You will be re-born in happy realms (from Anguttara Nikaya 11.</description></item><item><title>11 obstructions</title><link>https://www.dhammacharts.org/quartz/11/11-obstructions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.dhammacharts.org/quartz/11/11-obstructions/</guid><description>to spiritual growth for a monk:
There is the case where a monk is not well-versed in forms. He is unskilled in characteristics.</description></item><item><title>11 super normal (psychic) powers</title><link>https://www.dhammacharts.org/quartz/11/11-super-normal-psychic-powers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.dhammacharts.org/quartz/11/11-super-normal-psychic-powers/</guid><description>:1. Having been one, he becomes many 2. Having been many, he becomes one 3. He appears and vanishes 4. He goes unhindered through a wall, through an enclosure, through a mountain, as though through space 5.</description></item><item><title>11 things for concentration to grow</title><link>https://www.dhammacharts.org/quartz/11/11-things-for-concentration-to-grow/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.dhammacharts.org/quartz/11/11-things-for-concentration-to-grow/</guid><description>Keeping own body, behaviour, belongings and surroundings completely clean Having routine in recognizing the sign of calm and the sign of non-distraction Ballancing the abilities of faith vs.</description></item><item><title>11 things for energy to grow</title><link>https://www.dhammacharts.org/quartz/11/11-things-for-energy-to-grow/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.dhammacharts.org/quartz/11/11-things-for-energy-to-grow/</guid><description>Reflection on the long-term dangers of inactivity such as rebirth to a woeful state Reviewing the benefits to be gained by energetic praxis Remembering that no journey can ever be ended by a lazy one Giving credit to the good givers of the alms-food received Honoring the greatness of the prior effort of the Master Honoring the greatness of the prior effort of the lineage Removing laxity by perceiving light, change posture and open air Avoidance of slack, lazy, sluggish, negligent and careless people Friendship with enthusiastic, energetic and persistent people Reviewing the four right efforts often and systematically Commitment and resolute determination to arouse more energy (from Samyutta Nikaya 46)</description></item><item><title>11 things for joy to grow</title><link>https://www.dhammacharts.org/quartz/11/11-things-for-joy-to-grow/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.dhammacharts.org/quartz/11/11-things-for-joy-to-grow/</guid><description>: 1. Recollection of the supreme and sublime uniqueness of the Buddha. 2. Recollection of the supreme and sublime uniqueness of the Dhamma.</description></item></channel></rss>