<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>7s on</title><link>https://www.dhammacharts.org/quartz/7/</link><description>Recent content in 7s on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://www.dhammacharts.org/quartz/7/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>7 bases</title><link>https://www.dhammacharts.org/quartz/7/7-bases/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.dhammacharts.org/quartz/7/7-bases/</guid><description>Seven bases: 1. He discerns form 2. He discerns feeling 3. He discerns perception 4. He discerns fabrications 5. He discerns consciousness 6.</description></item><item><title>7 Directions</title><link>https://www.dhammacharts.org/quartz/7/7-directions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.dhammacharts.org/quartz/7/7-directions/</guid><description>The seven directions of loving-kindness meditation / prayer: 1. Yourself 2. Parents and/or children 3. Teachers 4. Relatives 5. Friends 6.</description></item><item><title>7 essential qualities (saddhamma)</title><link>https://www.dhammacharts.org/quartz/7/7-essential-qualities-saddhamma/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.dhammacharts.org/quartz/7/7-essential-qualities-saddhamma/</guid><description>faith moral shame – hiri fear of wrongdoing – ottappa great learning – bāhusacca energy – viriya mindfulness – sati wisdom 103D.</description></item><item><title>7 Factors of Enlightenment</title><link>https://www.dhammacharts.org/quartz/7/7-Factors-of-Enlightenment/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.dhammacharts.org/quartz/7/7-Factors-of-Enlightenment/</guid><description>Mindfulness Investigation Energy Rapture Calm Concentration Equanimity (from Digha Nikaya 16)</description></item><item><title>7 goals for developing the Noble Eightfold Middle Path</title><link>https://www.dhammacharts.org/quartz/7/7-goals-for-developing-the-Noble-Eightfold-Middle-Path/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.dhammacharts.org/quartz/7/7-goals-for-developing-the-Noble-Eightfold-Middle-Path/</guid><description>Having a good Dhamma friend (Kalyāna-mitta): Such friend has a pure and beautiful mind, which by simply being a good example will influence and encourage all other beings to improve their mentality, behaviour and understanding.</description></item><item><title>7 good qualities of a Dhamma follower</title><link>https://www.dhammacharts.org/quartz/7/7-good-qualities-of-a-Dhamma-follower/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.dhammacharts.org/quartz/7/7-good-qualities-of-a-Dhamma-follower/</guid><description> He has conviction, is convinced of the Tathagata&amp;rsquo;s Awakening He feels shame at [the thought of engaging in] bodily misconduct, verbal misconduct, mental misconduct He feels concern for [the suffering that results from] bodily misconduct, verbal misconduct, mental misconduct He has heard much, has retained what he has heard, has stored what he has heard He keeps his persistence aroused for abandoning unskillful mental qualities and taking on skillful mental qualities He is mindful, highly meticulous, remembering and able to call to mind even things that were done and said long ago He is discerning, endowed with discernment of arising and passing away — noble, penetrating, leading to the right ending of suffering</description></item><item><title>7 Kinds of Purity</title><link>https://www.dhammacharts.org/quartz/7/7-Kinds-of-Purity/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.dhammacharts.org/quartz/7/7-Kinds-of-Purity/</guid><description>Seven Kinds of Purity (M. I. 149-50; also, the entire text of the Visuddhimagga. At D. III. 289, two more kinds of purity are added at the end: paññā-visuddhi and vimutti-visuddhi.</description></item><item><title>7 qualities of a good friend</title><link>https://www.dhammacharts.org/quartz/7/7-qualities-of-a-good-friend/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.dhammacharts.org/quartz/7/7-qualities-of-a-good-friend/</guid><description>He gives what is hard to give He does what is hard to do He endures what is hard to endure He reveals his secrets to you He keeps your secrets When misfortunes strike, he doesn&amp;rsquo;t abandon you When you&amp;rsquo;re down and out, he doesn&amp;rsquo;t look down on you (from Anguttara Nikaya 7.</description></item><item><title>7 Seven latent tendencies</title><link>https://www.dhammacharts.org/quartz/7/7-Seven-latent-tendencies/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.dhammacharts.org/quartz/7/7-Seven-latent-tendencies/</guid><description>The latent tendency to sensual pleasure The latent tendency to aversion and ill-will The latent tendency to speculative views The latent tendency to skeptical doubt The latent tendency to conceiving ― I am The latent tendency to wanting to become The latent tendency to ignorance (from Samyutta Nikaya 45)</description></item><item><title>7 stations of consciousness</title><link>https://www.dhammacharts.org/quartz/7/7-stations-of-consciousness/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.dhammacharts.org/quartz/7/7-stations-of-consciousness/</guid><description>Diversity of body and diversity of perception (such as human beings, some devas, and some beings in the lower realms) Diversity of body and singularity of perception (such as the devas of the Brahma hosts generated by the first jhana and some beings in the four realms of deprivation) Beings with singularity of body and diversity of perception (such as the Radiant Devas) Beings with singularity of body and singularity of perception (such as the Beautifully Lustrous Devas) Beings who, with the complete transcending of perceptions of [physical] form, with the disappearance of perceptions of resistance, and not heeding perceptions of diversity, [perceiving] Infinite space, arrive at the dimension of the infinitude of space Beings who, with the complete transcending of the dimension of the infinitude of space, [perceiving] Infinite consciousness, arrive at the dimension of the infinitude of consciousness Beings who, with the complete transcending of the dimension of the infinitude of consciousness, [perceiving] there is no-thing, arrive at the dimension of nothingness (from Digha Nikaya 15)</description></item></channel></rss>